<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<welcomePage title="FIS Application Studio">
	<intro>This page will help familiarize you with the FIS Application Studio.
To get started, read the sections below and click on the related links. </intro>
	<item>
		<b>What is FIS Application Studio </b>
FIS Application Studio is a fully integrated development environment for developing 
functionality in FIS Profile. To find out more about the features installed in your 
workbench, choose <action pluginId="org.eclipse.ui" class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.QuickStartAction">Help > Welcome...</action> and select the feature you are interested in.</item>
	<item>
		<b>What's New in 3.0</b>
Learn about the new feature in version 3.0 in the <topic id="/com.fnf.profile.ide/doc/userGuide.xml">Profile Development User Guide</topic>
	</item>
	<item>
		<b>FIS Profile Perspective</b> 
The default perspective contains views geared toward FIS Profile Development. To learn more about 
these features you can browse the <topic id="/com.fnf.profile.ide/doc/userGuide.xml">Profile Development User Guide</topic>.</item>
	<item>
		<b>PSL Development</b> 
Developing in Profile Scripting Language (PSL) has never been easier. On-line help is embedded 
in the FIS Application Studio. You can access this through the Help menu, or directly at 
<topic id="/com.fnf.profile.ide.help/pslhelp_xml/toc.xml">PSL Help</topic>.</item>
	<item>
		<b>FIS Programming Standards</b> 
You can browse <topic id="/com.fnf.profile.ide.help/standards_xml/toc.xml">FIS Programming Standards </topic> to learn about standards and guidelines 
for programming Profile applications.</item>
	<item>
		<b>Eclipse Platform</b>
The FIS Application Studio is built on Eclipse Technology. This means you have all the power 
of Eclipse in addition to features specifically tailored for FIS Application development.

To learn more you can browse the <topic id="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/toc.xml">Workbench User Guide</topic>.</item>
</welcomePage>
